https://www.inmaricopa.com/privacy/

password
Forgot your password?
user name
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Sign in
Welcome to InMaricopa! Login to your account.
user name
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Password recovery
Recover your password
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Privacy Statement
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ). This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) does not read any of your private online communications.
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) and InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) collects and uses your personal information to operate the InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) Web site and deliver the services you have requested. InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) and its affiliates. InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ), and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ), in order to determine what InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ), or the public.
Use of Cookies
The InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) pages, or register with InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) site or services, a cookie helps InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) is protecting your information.
Contact Information
InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) has not adhered to this Statement, please contact InMaricopa.com Maricopa Arizona (AZ) at newwebsite@InMaricopa.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
18,119FansLike3,718FollowersFollow2,037FollowersFollow538SubscribersSubscribe Events
To find awesome listings near you!
